   <quests>
      <quest id="0">
         <start>
	         #Stranger# Oh, hello there...=>
	         #Stranger# Uhm... I haven't seen you here before, who are you?=>
	         #Stranger# Well, to be honest, it doesn't matter. Not in this place.=>
	         #Richard# My name is... uhm... Dick, but I don't really like it. Call me Richard.=>
	         #Richard# You seem lost... You know what? If you can prove you can be of any use, then we'll talk.=>
	         #Richard# Can you please bring me some wood for the campfire? Here's an axe, it'll help you.=>
	         #Richard# Return to me when you get 15 wood pieces.=>
	         * You can gather wood by taking axe in your hands (open inventory with E key and left click the axe), approaching a tree and hitting enter a few times.
         </start>
         <complete>
	         #Richard# Thanks a lot, stranger.=>
	         #Richard# I'd like to know your name now...=>
	         #Richard# Nice to meet you, {PLAYER}!=>
	         #Richard# Hm... Okay. You can take my axe as a reward. It's old anyways. If you want some job or a good story, just ask!
         </complete>
         <requirement>1/15</requirement>
         <give_items>3/1</give_items>
         <remove_on_completion>n</remove_on_completion>
         <repeatable>False</repeatable>
         <next>1</next>
         <reward>n</reward>
         <reward_exp>20</reward_exp>
         <requirement_str>
         	#Richard# Please, give me 15 wood pieces.
         </requirement_str>
      </quest>
      <quest id="1">
         <start>
	         #Richard# Hello, {PLAYER}!=>
	         #Richard# You know, our camp gets raided by Marauders pretty frequently. But now that you appeared out of nowhere, I've got a strange feeling that we have a chance against them!=>
	         #Richard# Go kill 10 rookie marauders to scare them off. Then we'll begin to plan something bigger.
         </start>
         <complete>
         	#Richard# Thank you, hero! Take your reward and return to me when you are ready for the next task.
         </complete>
         <requirement>22/10</requirement>
         <give_items>2/5</give_items>
         <reward>n</reward>
         <reward_exp>50</reward_exp>
         <repeatable>False</repeatable>
         <requirement_str>
         	#Richard# Kill 10 marauders and give me 10 leather pieces you get from them.
         </requirement_str>
      </quest>
   </quests>